<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>

  <!--Effect description notes: 
   - these are added to the in-game description of mythic items, after the flavor string.
   - The element {0} should always be the label of the mythic item itself (ex: Revolver).
   - All other elements can vary depending on what subtype of mythic effect def uses these,
   although {1} should try to be the label of whatever is added to this weapon (ex a hediff, or ability label), if applicable. -->
  <MooMF_AbilityDescription_Addon>\n\nMythic Effect: {0}</MooMF_AbilityDescription_Addon>
  <MooMF_AbilityDescription_GrantStatAbility>Grants the user the "{1}" buff, which passively improves their performance in the relevant skill.</MooMF_AbilityDescription_GrantStatAbility>
  <MooMF_AbilityDescription_GrantThurmboButcher>Grants the user the "{1}" buff, which doubles their butcher yields from thrumbos.</MooMF_AbilityDescription_GrantThurmboButcher>
  <MooMF_AbilityDescription_GrantEpicureanWisdom>Grants the user the "{1}" buff, which allows them to cook epicurean delights.</MooMF_AbilityDescription_GrantEpicureanWisdom>
  <MooMF_AbilityDescription_MechDrops>This weapon makes the user unusually good at dismantling mechanoids. When they kill a mechanoid, it will drop extra steel, and possibly other things.</MooMF_AbilityDescription_MechDrops>
  <MooMF_AbilityDescription_InsectDrops>This weapon grants the user a supernatural instinct for finding extra insect jelly, which is dropped whenever they kill an insect. Just don't ask where it comes from.</MooMF_AbilityDescription_InsectDrops>
  <MooMF_AbilityDescription_Thrumbocall>This {0} grants the user the "{1}" ability, which summons a thrumbo herd up to once a year. This effect has no impact on normal Thrumbo migration frequencies.</MooMF_AbilityDescription_Thrumbocall>
  <MooMF_AbilityDescription_APRocket>This {0} has a small grapeshot rocket jury-rigged onto its side, granting the "{1}" ability. This can be used once a day deal heavy damage to unarmored foes.</MooMF_AbilityDescription_APRocket>
  <MooMF_AbilityDescription_EMPRocket>This {0} has a small EMP cannon jury-rigged onto its side, granting the "{1}" ability. This can be used once a day to immobolize a large cluster of mechanoids for significantly more time than other EMP weapons.</MooMF_AbilityDescription_EMPRocket>
  <MooMF_AbilityDescription_KillstreakDR>While equipped, this {0}'s user enters a battle trance every time they kill something, granting damage resistance. Subsequent kills before it wears off will increase the effect.</MooMF_AbilityDescription_KillstreakDR>
  <MooMF_AbilityDescription_KillstreakFirerate>While equipped, this {0}'s user enters a battle trance every time they kill something, granting improved fire rates and firing cooldown. Subsequent kills before it wears off will increase the effect.</MooMF_AbilityDescription_KillstreakFirerate>
  <MooMF_AbilityDescription_KillstreakSpeed>While equipped, this {0}'s user enters a battle trance every time they kill something, granting increased movespeed. Subsequent kills before it wears off will increase the effect.</MooMF_AbilityDescription_KillstreakSpeed>
  <MooMF_AbilityDescription_AttactTradeShips>This {0} has some special radio codes embroidered into it. Anyone wearing it can occasionally use these codes to attract a nearby merchant ship into trading range.</MooMF_AbilityDescription_AttactTradeShips>
  <MooMF_AbilityDescription_TamingInspiration>This {0} contains the vestiges of an animal master's wisdom. A wearer can draw upon this wisdom to immediately gain a taming inspiration.</MooMF_AbilityDescription_TamingInspiration>
  <MooMF_AbilityDescription_CreativeInspiration>This {0} contains a master crafter's insight. A wearer can draw upon this insight to immediately gain a creative inspirtion.</MooMF_AbilityDescription_CreativeInspiration>
  <MooMF_AbilityDescription_ShootingInspiration>The instincts of a peerless sniper are hewn into this {0}. A wielder can draw upon these instincts to grant a shooting inspiration to theirself and their companions.</MooMF_AbilityDescription_ShootingInspiration>
  <MooMF_AbilityDescription_GrantHerdFeedersWisdom>Grants the user the "{1}" buff, which allows them to produce kibble with miraculous efficiency.</MooMF_AbilityDescription_GrantHerdFeedersWisdom>
  <MooMF_AbilityDescription_Prospecting>This {0} grants the user the "{1}" ability, which can be used every few days to immediatly find an underground mineral deposit.</MooMF_AbilityDescription_Prospecting>
  <MooMF_AbilityDescription_KillstreakHealing>While equipped, this {0}'s user enters a battle trance every time they kill something, granting a huge natural healing boost. Old stories about this weapon claim that heartless warriors recoved from intense battles by killing their pets. But surely you wouldn't do that... would you?</MooMF_AbilityDescription_KillstreakHealing>



</LanguageData>