<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>
  <!--In mythic stories, the following variables always apply to the following features
    0 = the original owner's full name
    1 = the original owners nickname, or first name if they don't have one
    2 = the original owner's faction
    3 = normal item label 
    -->
 
  <!-- kill threshold descriptions-->
  <!-- human kills tier 1-->
  <MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills1_Melee_1>It's said that {0} of {2}, the original owner of this {3}, used it to butcher over a hundred people. That seems far-fetched, but it's undeniable that this weapon has been wielded in untold battles. The fact that nobody can entirely clean off all the bloodstains lends credence to the legends.</MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills1_Melee_1>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills1_Melee_2>No one believed the stories about them, but this {3} is stark evidence of what the people of {2} were capable of. The name {1} is carved into the handle of this {3}, just barely legible after untold years of hard use.</MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills1_Melee_2>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills1_Melee_3>This {3} might have once had intricate ornamentation, but the details have been eroded away across its long history of bloodshed. Despite the obvious wear and tear, however, a small metal plate bearing the name {1} still stands out clearly in the design.</MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills1_Melee_3>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills1_Melee_4>Anyone who holds this {3} will surely notice how comfortably it fits in the hand. Given the legends told about {2} and the constant strife they faced, it's no surprise that {0}'s long use of this weapon molded the grip to fit the grasp of a killer.</MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills1_Melee_4>

  <MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills1_Ranged_1>This ancient {3} is etched with more tally marks than you can count. That's not too surprising, since {0} - the original wielder of this arnament - was said to have been quite the show off. Now it's time for you to break their record.</MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills1_Ranged_1>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills1_Ranged_2>You've heard many tales about {0}, the headhunter of {2}. Everyone thought the stories about them were just that - stories. But now, with {1}'s {3} rediscovered, people can't help but wonder if those tall tales were true. This weapon oozes bloodlust, and you shudder to guess how many last moments were seen from the sights of this weapon.</MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills1_Ranged_2>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills1_Ranged_3>You've heard many stories about {1}, the headhunter of {2}. It's hard to believe the stories were true, but the sense of bloodlust emenating from this {3} suggests that more than a few people died from this weapon's shots.</MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills1_Ranged_3>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills1_Ranged_4>Given that this {3} has over a hundred bloodstained notches in its stock, one has to wonder how the people of {2} made so many enemies. Regardless of the reasons, the legends told of {0} and their monstrous ability to gun down said enemies clearly have some truth to them.</MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills1_Ranged_4>
  <!-- human kills tier 2-->
  <MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills2_Melee_M1>How strong was {1}, the Butcher of {2}? No one is sure, because no one faced them and lived. The only truth you can find is in this {3}, which is weathered and chipped from thousands of strikes. It clearly served its purpose well, and will likely continue to do so, should you have the strength to use it.</MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills2_Melee_M1>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills2_Melee_M2>Many Rimworlders like to call themselves warriors, but few actually survive the brutal tests of time to earn that title. But this {3} once belonged to a true warrior named {0}. Tribal myths claim that {1} ferociously defended the people of {2} and left legions of dead raiders in their wake. Hopefully their {3} will help you defend your colony as well.</MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills2_Melee_M2>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills2_Melee_1>Stories told about {2} inevitably touch on two things: their incredible capacity for violence, and the efficiency with which {0} cut through foes using a {3}. Though the name inscribed on the grip has all but faded, there is no question that this {3} is the very weapon which once belonged to {1}.</MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills2_Melee_1>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills2_Melee_2>In watering holes across the Rim, hushed stories are told of {0} and the countless lives they ended. Though some of the legends have surely grown to be far larger than life, the condition of this {3} clearly shows that {1} was an adept killer of men.</MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills2_Melee_2>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills2_Melee_3>This {3} feels as if it is radiating an unnatural need for blood. Merely holding it in your hand calls to mind tales of the legendary butcher {0} of {2}, urging the wielder to ever greater feats of slaughter.</MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills2_Melee_3>

  <MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills2_Ranged_M1>People like to brag about having "{1}'s trigger finger", which is a reference to {0}, a storied sharpshooter of the Rim. This {3} actually belonged to them, and even though the rifling of the barrel is smooth from firing countless shots, it still aims flawlessly.</MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills2_Ranged_M1>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills2_Ranged_1>  </MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills2_Ranged_1>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills2_Ranged_2>  </MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills2_Ranged_2>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills2_Ranged_3>  </MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills2_Ranged_3>
  <!-- human kills tier 3-->
  <MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills3_Melee_M1>The God of War. Corpse-Bringer. The Hound of {2}. These are just a few of the titles earned by the legendary killer named {0}. It's hard to believe that they were a real person, and even harder to believe that you somehow found their long-lost {3}. Picking it up, this {3} feels like a natural extension of your body. Clearly it's more than ready to continue drawing blood in {1}'s name.</MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills3_Melee_M1>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills3_Melee_M2>The name "{1}" is a slang for bad luck among raiders, thanks to old folk tales about a monstrous pirate-killer named {0}. They're said to have killed more raiders than should logically exist on any one rimworld. Is it happens, this old {3} fit the description of {1}'s long-lost weapon, so hopefully you can use it to start some new slang soon.</MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills3_Melee_M2>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills3_Melee_1>This {3} does strike true
    as {1} brings death anew
    If they decide
    to have your hide
    They'll make their clothes of you!</MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills3_Melee_1>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills3_Melee_2>A palpable sense of menace emanates from this {3}, as if the weapon itself begs to be bathed in the blood of enemies. Simply reading the name {1} inscribed in this weapon sends a chill down the spine, and the stories told of {2} leaves no doubt that this {3} has seen more war than many entire armies.</MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills3_Melee_2>
 
  <MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills3_RangedM1>Have you heard the story of {1} the Grim? Of course not. It's not a tale the raiders would tell you. It's a Rimworlder legend. {0} was a lord of the {2}, so powerful and so accurate that they could use their {3} to create death on an incomparable scale. They had such a knowledge of violence that they could even keep the ones they cared about from dying on the Rim. Absolute violence is a pathway to many abilities some consider to be unnatural, and this {3} is evidence of that.</MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills3_RangedM1>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills3_Ranged_1>  </MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills3_Ranged_1>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills3_Ranged_2>  </MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills3_Ranged_2>

  <!-- Insect kills tier 1-->
  <MooMF_MythicStory_InsectKills1_MeleeM1>Insect hives are a concern for all Rimworld colonies, but some colonies fear the bugs less than others. The "{2}" faction in particular was known for producing mountains of insect meat. Apparently one of their warriors - a {3}-wielding killer named {0} - was very adept at squashing every bug that burrowed into their lands. Now their chitin-encrusted {3} has somehow found itself here, and you feel a sudden urge to go tick off the nearest hive...</MooMF_MythicStory_InsectKills1_MeleeM1>

  <MooMF_MythicStory_InsectKills1_RangedM1>Most people like to deal with giant insects with fire. Lots of fire. But some people like using lead. Lots of metaphorical lead. {1} the exterminator was known for using both techniques, and their trusty {3} has seen the fall of insect colonies across multiple centuries and Rimworlds.</MooMF_MythicStory_InsectKills1_RangedM1>

  <!-- Insect kills tier 2-->
  <MooMF_MythicStory_InsectKills2_MeleeM1>Grand queens are a type of giant insect most Rimworlders have only heard about. They never leave their hives, are the size of a whale, and can easily slaughter platoons of imperial janissaries with their enormous mandibles and bulletproof chitin. But at least one person has killed a grand queen. Long ago, an lone Rimworlder of no renown ventured into a hive on their own, seeking glory. After ten days, their fiends assumed the worst, but on the eleventh day, they returned. Their clothing was practically ribbons, and their body covered in wounds, but their trusty {3} was still intact, and behind them they dragged out a grand queen's head. Thus the legend of {0} the Queenslayer was born.</MooMF_MythicStory_InsectKills2_MeleeM1>
  
  <MooMF_MythicStory_InsectKills2_RangedM1>Have you ever fought an insect hive that was infested with Megamantises and Ultraspiders? No, you haven't, and you can thank {1} the Queenslayer for that. {0} was a legendary hunter, and supposedly they caused the extinction of multiple giant insect species. This {3} is what they used when they were first getting started. Make sure you treat it with respect.</MooMF_MythicStory_InsectKills2_RangedM1>

  <!-- mech kills tier 1-->
  <MooMF_MythicStory_MechKills1_MeleeM1></MooMF_MythicStory_MechKills1_MeleeM1>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_MechKills1_MeleeM2></MooMF_MythicStory_MechKills1_MeleeM2>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_MechKills1_RangedM1></MooMF_MythicStory_MechKills1_RangedM1>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_MechKills1_RangedM2></MooMF_MythicStory_MechKills1_RangedM2>
  
  <!-- mech kills tier 2-->
  <MooMF_MythicStory_MechKills2_MeleeM1></MooMF_MythicStory_MechKills2_MeleeM1>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_MechKills2_MeleeM2></MooMF_MythicStory_MechKills2_MeleeM2>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_MechKills2_RangedM1></MooMF_MythicStory_MechKills2_RangedM1>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_MechKills2_RangedM2></MooMF_MythicStory_MechKills2_RangedM2>
  
  <!-- thrumbo kills -->
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Kills_Thrumbos_1>Stories about {0} crop up in tribal folklore, where "{1} the Horn-Taker"  is feared as a slayer of nature spirits. Depending on your opinion of thrumbos, that might be true, as {0}'s ancient {3} is decorated with the weathered bones of no less than three adult thrumbos.</MooMF_MythicStory_Kills_Thrumbos_1>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Kills_Thrumbos_M2>It's said that thrumbos avoid all settlements of {2}. It's easy to see why. This {3} used to belong to one of their champions - a hunter named {0}. Simply holding this {3} gives you an urge to go on a thurmbo hunt. You can only imagine how many of the creatures must have been felled by this weapon to inbue it with such energy.</MooMF_MythicStory_Kills_Thrumbos_M2>

  <!--{1}. Ready. Shoot. Pain.
Fall. Squeel. Flee. Blame.
{1}. Ready. Shoot. Dead.
Fall. Sleep. Bleed. Red.Breath. Again. Take. Aim.
Let. Loose. Lead. Rain.-->

  <MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills3_RangedM2>Have you heard of the Ghost of {2}? Supposedly they were a sniper who claimed hundreds of lives across the Rim, ripping through pirates like tissue paper with their trusty {3}. How that artifact ended up here is anyone's guess, but it still tears through raiders as easily as ever.</MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills3_RangedM2>


  <!-- skill descriptions-->
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Shooting_1>The last owner of this {3} said that it had been collecting dust in storage for decades, yet it is still in pristine condition. They also claim this {3} belonged to the legendary sharpshooter named {0}. The stories about {1} mention that they were obsessive about maintaining their gear, so perhaps this weapon's supernatural cleanliness lends credence to those tales.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Shooting_1>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Shooting_2>The case for this {3} contains not only the weapon itself, but also targets, spare ammunition, repair tools, and cleaning supplies that could cover any conceivable need. It is clear that {0} was not only an excellent shot, but also a master of firearm maintenance and someone who deeply appreciated the art of shooting.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Shooting_2>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Shooting_3>Accompanying this {3} was hastily sketched advertisement for "{0}'s Firearms" with the slogan "Come let {1} make your gun shoot good!" While it's unclear if this fledgling business ever got off the ground, there's no question that {0} was an expert marksman, and their {3} does indeed "shoot good" to this day.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Shooting_3>

  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Melee_1>There are old bedtime stories about "{1} the Mighty", the greatest fighter who ever lived. Most people thought they were just that - stories - until this {3} showed up. If the engraving on this ancient weapon is to be believed, {2} were a real group of people, and {1} was a paragon of battle among their number.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Melee_1>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Melee_M1>In a historic upset, the winner of the First Grand Imperial Gladiatorial Tournament was a Rimworlder named {0} from a faction of little renown called {2}. {1} swept through the tournament with their trusty {3} like a whirlwind. As it happens, this {3} matches the descriptions of {1}'s weapon. It must have been stolen from the Imperial museum where it had been on display, and wound up on another Rimworld.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Melee_M1>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Melee_2>Records unearthed from an ancient fighting ring indicate that one fighter, {0}, went undefeated in nearly a hundred melee fights of various styles. It's unclear whether these feats were accomplished prior to, during, or after {1}'s time in the Rim, but it is abundantly clear from the condition of this {3} that their martial prowess was no myth.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Melee_2>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Melee_3>A popular glitterworld holo-film tells the tale of a depressed colonist named {0}, equipped only with a {3}, who defiantly defends the beleaguered Rimworld colony of {2}. As cannibal tribals, gnashing insectoids, and mechanical nightmares alike fall before their fury, {1} realizes their true purpose is to master melee combat in all its forms, and they eventually ascend in glory to serve the Empire as a master-at-arms. This {3} looks awfully like the one from the story, and its killing prowess indicates it's no mere prop...</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Melee_3>
  <!--, taking down royal guards, veteran capharact shock troppers, and grizzled pirates without breaking a sweat-->
  
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Construction_1>No matter how many times you empty out the extra pockets of this {3}, you always seem to find another nail, screw, or loose piece of wire. You aren't sure if it's magical, or if the master architect known as {0} simply stuffed more random building scraps into this clothing than you thought possible.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Construction_1>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Construction_M2>Imperial nobles like to brag about owning homes with {1}-ish architecture, or furniture that is "built in the {2}-ian style". These boasts hark back to the constructions of {0}, the greatest builder of the Rim. Based on the dusty blueprints that were left in the pockets of this {3}, this apparel actually once belonged to {1}, and even today it still inspires people to build grand monuments.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Construction_M2>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Construction_2>After being excavated, researchers noted that ruins of the colony of {2} have one peculiarity: nearly every brick, beam, and board seems to be signed or stamped with the name of one "{0}." Anyone wearing this {3}, likewise stamped as once being property of {1}, will surely be inspired by their tenacity and attention to detail in construction.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Construction_2>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Construction_3>Although not well-preserved, the ruins of the {2} colony show remarkable craftsmanship, and historians are quick to note that nearly every structure present was made to the precise specifications of their chief engineer {0}. This {3}, also recovered from the ruins, remains in extremely good condition, a fact likely also due to {1}'s exacting nature.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Construction_3>

  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Mining_1>The words "Who needs the sun?" are legible on a faded patch on this {3}. Perhaps that philosophy drove {0} to become the best miner anyone has ever heard of. Rim-hoppers claim that {1} single-handedly dug up enough steel to build a space ship. As it happens, this {3} is roughly 50% steel dust by weight, so you're inclined to believe those stories.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Mining_1>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Mining_M2>"Beware fate of {2}. Led by {0}, the great tunneller of yore, they dug too deep, and lost sight of the stars. Heed not the tempting whispers of their keepsake {3}, lest you too dig too deep."
That's an old story from multiple tribal cultures on the Rim. The true fate of {2} is unknown, but it's also true that this old {3} gives you an odd urge to dig. Perhaps just a small underground fortress will be good enough...</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Mining_M2>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Mining_2>Legendary colonies such as {2} require countless resources, and when it came to mining them, none were more renowned than {0}. This {3} that once belonged to them is host to numerous patches and repairs, yet still flows around the wearer flawlessly as they swing a pick into compacted steel.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Mining_2>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Mining_3>  </MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Mining_3>

  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Cooking_1>Some of your colonists find this {3} unnerving. Even after being washed a dozed times, the smell of corn still clings to it. That's because it once belonged to the interstellar gourmet sensation known simply as {1}, who is rumored to have cooked more food than most people have ever eaten.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Cooking_1>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Cooking_2>To this day, gourmet restaurants across the Rim are rated according to a system of one to three "{1} Stars." While some insist {1} was the founder of a tire company, the truth is that they belonged to a colony known as {2}, where they prepared gourmet meals day in and day out wearing this very {3}.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Cooking_2>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Cooking_3>Some tell stories of how much of a menace {0} could be in the kitchen - strutting around in this {3} as they called fellow colonists "idiot sandwiches" or insisting that even the most perfectly cooked meat was "fookin raw." However, none among {2} could deny that the meals {1} produced were of the highest quality, and they remain respected as a chef across the Rim to this day.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Cooking_3>

  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Plants_1>This {3} is covered in mossy dirt stains - a testament to the dedication of "{1} the Green-Thumbed". Legends tell of the people of {2}, who never went hungry thanks to {1}'s skill. Loose seeds leaking out of this {3} endless, so perhaps a kernel of truth to those tales.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Plants_1>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Plants_M2>Legends claim that a lost city lies in the middle of the {1}-ian Jungle. Supposedly the jungle sprang up from the city itself, thanks to the tireless efforts of {0}, a botanist of extraordinary skill. The only artifact left of that city is this {3}, which smells like a lush plant growth.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Plants_M2>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Plants_2>Some people are simply blessed with the ability to make plants flourish, and few across the galaxy were moreso gifted than {0}. Legends tell tales of the bounteous harvests the people of {2} enjoyed due to {1}'s skilled tending. Hopefully some of their skill transfers to you as you wear this {3} bearing their name.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Plants_2>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Plants_3>Despite being caked in a layer of soil that no scrubbing could ever fully clean off, these {3} fit perfectly and afford the utmost ease when gardening. It's clear that {1}, whose name adorns the {3} like a flower atop a stem, used them to expertly cultivate plants for the entire colony of {2}.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Plants_3>

  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Animals_1>DNA analysis has confirmed that the fur, scales, and feathers embroidered into this {3} originated from no less than a dozen different animal species. Perhaps all the campfire tales about {1} - the greatest animal handler of the Rim - were true. After all, only someone of that caliber could have tamed so many different creatures.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Animals_1>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Animals_M2>Old planet-hopping raiders like to spook new recruits with stories about the maniacs of {2}. Legions of animals defended their colonies, thanks to a peerless shepherd named {0} who tamed all manner of beasts. This ratty {3} seems related to those old stories, as there's a patch with the name {1} sewn onto it, and people who wear this {3} claim to feel unusualy calm around pets and other critters.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Animals_M2>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Animals_2>Animal husbandry textbooks have countless techniques named after {0}, and nearly every image in such volumes pictures them wearing these {3}. Perhaps if you don them yourself you will gain a measure of {1}'s fabled ability to pacify and tend to animals of all types.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Animals_2>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Animals_3>  </MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Animals_3>

  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Crafting_1>Just holding {0}'s old {3} makes your fingers twitch with the desire to craft something. Apparently the instincts of {1}, the greatest tinker from the fabled civilization of {2}, have been passed into their gear.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Crafting_1>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Crafting_M2>If you have to ask how much some gear made from {0} would cost, then you can't afford it. But that's not surprising; no one on the Rim can afford a real {1}-ian. Their craftsmanship is legendary. Of course that begs the question of how {1}'s own {3} ended up here, but why worry about that when you can brag to your friends instead?</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Crafting_M2>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Crafting_2>The name {0} appears in hobbyist handbooks everywhere, from weapon fabrication manuals to garment sewing patterns. This {3}, recovered from the ruins of {2} and itself undoubtably originally crafted by {1}'s deft hands, imbues the wearer with the uncanny desire to take things apart and put them back together again.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Crafting_2>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Crafting_3>Nearly everything recovered from the ruins of the {2} colony, including this {3}, bears the name {1}. It seems this one person was responsible for creating or overseeing the creation of nearly everything the colony used, a feat wearing this {3} compels you to match.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Crafting_3>


  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Artistic_1>Some of the most expensive sculptures in interstellar history were made by an artist named {0}. Most people thought this name was an alias, but the faded, whimsically painted name on this {3} suggests otherwise. Just wearing {1}'s clothing seems to magically produce paint stains and marble dust everywhere, but it also instills a creative drive to meet the expectations you know {0} would have.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Artistic_1>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Artistic_M2>How impressive is {0}'s artistic reputation? Well, if you have to ask how much one {1}-ian statue costs, then you can't afford it. Known for touring glitterworlds and Imperial Fleets to showcase their masterpieces, {0} is a true rags-to-riches success story of the Rim. </MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Artistic_M2>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Artistic_2>Despite living most of their creative life on a nondescript Rim planet, {0} has a clear place in the pantheon of legendary artists of the galaxy. Their name circulates often as one of the all-time greats, and wearing this {3} that once belonged to them is sure to inspire anyone to reach that same lofty pinnacle of artistic talent.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Artistic_2>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Artistic_3>{0} of {2} was a sculpture and painting master so widely known, so universally beloved, that they recieved the highest honor an artist can receive: having a children's cartoon turtle named after them. Though these {3} once belonging to {0} will not bestow ninja powers or a radical protective shell, they definitely inspire the wearer to live up to the standards {1}'s enduring works of art represent.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Artistic_3>

  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Medicine_1>This {3} was once worn by {0}, the legendary surgeon of {2}. The countless tally marks on the {3} - originally asuumed to be counting kills - are now thought to be a count of lives saved (or possibly organs harvested, you never know around here).</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Medicine_1>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Medicine_2>{0} is well-known in the medical community, as an entire subfield of emergency anesthetic and amputation techniques bears their name. Although this is just an ordinary {3}, seeing the weathered name "{1}" on the breast pocket brings huge measure of confidence to anyone performing those very procedures.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Medicine_2>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Medicine_3>Awash in a sea of shot, bruised, and cut colonists, it is said that the community of {2} would have surely fallen in days were it not for the efforts of one heroic doctor named {0}. This {3} bearing their name has been bleached nearly white after being sterilized countless times, but wearing it nonetheless imbues you with {1}'s legendary sense of aesculapian pride.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Medicine_3>

  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Social_1>Everyone has heard stories about the Bard of {2}. They could pacify mechs with words, peacefully trade with cannibal tribes, and married into the High Stellarch's family. Perhaps {0} - which is the Bard's real name - exaggerated a few of those stories. But there must have been at least a little truth to behind them, because {1}'s charismatic energy definitely still lingers in this {3}.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Social_1>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Social_2>Though the colony of {2} has long been lost to time, tales of {1}'s bright smile and welcoming demeanor still circulate the Rim to this day. Seeing someone wearing this fine {3} inevitably brightens anyone's day, and it is almost as if the clothes themselves compel the wearer to live up to the legends of {1}'s hospitality.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Social_2>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Social_3>Legends say {1} wore the freshest clothes, ate at the chillest restaurants, and hung out with the hottest dudes. They were jacked and anybody who talked shit about them was pathetic. Nobody would say shit to {1}, and now that you're wearing their {3}, the same can be said of you.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Social_3>

  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Intellectual_1>{1} is a name that's rarely mentioned. Only Cryptic archotechs allude to them when discussing their original creators. {0}'s brilliance must have been unmmatched, and this {3} is the first evidence that they were a real person, and not just an archotech bedtime story.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Intellectual_1>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Intellectual_M2>Many Rimworlders like to thank "{1} the Inventor" for the few conveniences that exist on the Rim. They're credited with inventing the auto-spork, among other things. You're inclined to believe those rumors, since this {3} has some old hand-written schematics for a prototypical auto-spork nestled in a pocket, and they're signed with {0}'s initials.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Intellectual_M2>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Intellectual_M3>Many Rimworlders like to thank "{1} the Inventor" for the few conveniences that exist on the Rim. They're credited with inventing the laser umbrella, among other things. You're inclined to believe those rumors, since this {3} has some old hand-written schematics for a prototypical laser umbrella nestled in a pocket, and they're signed with {0}'s initials.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Intellectual_M3>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Intellectual_M4>Many Rimworlders like to thank "{1} the Inventor" for the few conveniences that exist on the Rim. They're credited with inventing the shark-proof flak vest, among other things. You're inclined to believe those rumors, since this {3} contains some old hand-written schematics for the fish-proof flak vest (a precursor of the modern shark-proof flak vest), and they're signed with {0}'s initials.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Intellectual_M4>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Intellectual_M5>Many Rimworlders like to thank "{1} the Inventor" for the few conveniences that exist on the Rim. They're credited with inventing reuseable toothpaste, among other things. You're inclined to believe those rumors, since this {3} has some old hand-written schematics for double-use toothpaste nestled in a pocket, and it's signed with {0}'s initials.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Intellectual_M5>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Intellectual_2>{0} was never a huge name in the research community, credited in only a few papers that rarely circlate the Rim. Among those in the know, however, {1} had a stellar reputation for the unmatched brilliance of their work, and the condition of this {3} indicates they probably spent more time implementing their research at home with the people of {2} rather than authoring scholarly articles.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Intellectual_2>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Intellectual_3>The name {0} appears in archotechnology textbooks of all levels, but few traces have ever been found of {2} or the researcher that propelled them into an intellectual renaissance. The badge on this {3} clearly reads "{1}" however, and anyone with the rare honor to wear the clothes {0} once did is sure to be inspired to achieve intellectually as they once did.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Intellectual_3>


  <!-- misc descriptions-->
  <MooMF_MythicStory_ThrumboFriend_1>Many tribes around the Rim worship a spirit called "{1}, Friend of the Wise". Myths about this character date back to the lost settlements of {2}, whose people supposedly knew how to befriend and even tame the majestic thrumbo. This plain-looking {3} seems to attract thrumbos, so perhaps the myths were true.</MooMF_MythicStory_ThrumboFriend_1>

  <!--- victory descriptions-->
  <MooMF_MythicDescription_SpaceVictory_1>It is said that the people of {2} were one of the few Rim factions to have the grit, brains, and the metaphysical patience to build or find a spaceship and successfully get off a Rimworld. No one from their original planet knows where they went, but this {3} from {1} - one of the escapees - proves that they did eventually reach another planet. Perhaps it was this planet, sometime in the distant past.</MooMF_MythicDescription_SpaceVictory_1>

  <MooMF_MythicDescription_RoyalVictory_M1>Life aboard the Imperial Flotilla is an existence of unparalleled extravagance and splendor. Of course it's rare for any Rimworlder to earn such a life, and rarer still for their belongings to somehow end up back on another Rimworld. This {3} is the only known example of such an item. People think that it was misplaced by a Regal Rimworlder named {0} after a wild night that storytellers call "The greatest autobong glitter-bender of all time". What exactly happened on that night? That's for you to not know, and for {1} to probably not remember either.</MooMF_MythicDescription_RoyalVictory_M1>

  <MooMF_MythicDescription_ArchoVictory_M1>Some people consider this {3} to be evidence of the hubris of unfettered technology. Others call it a manifestation of the divine. Debates aside, it's clear that this object has been exposed to an unfathomable amount of psychic energy, which makes it difficult to even look at for too long. Wearing it connects the user's mind to the echoes of a distant archotech that refers to itself as "{1} 2.0". This archotech offers all sort of advice, and also occasionally mentions a group of people known as {2}. Perhaps one of them was the original owner of this {3}.</MooMF_MythicDescription_ArchoVictory_M1>



</LanguageData>