[[<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>
  <!--In mythic stories, the following variables always apply to the following features
    0 = the original owner's full name
    1 = the original owners nickname, or first name if they don't have one
    2 = the original owner's faction
    3 = normal item label 
    -->
[[
  <MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills1_Melee_1>It's said that {0} of {2}, the original owner of this {3}, used it to butcher over a hundred people. That seems far-fetched, but it's undeniable that this weapon has been wielded in untold battles. The fact that nobody can entirely clean off all the bloodstains lends credence to the legends.</MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills1_Melee_1>

  <MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills1_Melee_2>No one believed the stories about them, but this {3} is stark evidence of what the people of {2} were capable of. The name {1} is carved into the handle of this {3}, just barely legible after untold years of hard use.</MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills1_Melee_2>

  <MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills1_Melee_3>This {3} might have once had intricate ornamentation, but the details have been eroded away across its long history of bloodshed. Despite the obvious wear and tear, however, a small metal plate bearing the name {1} still stands out clearly in the design.</MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills1_Melee_3>

  <MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills1_Melee_4>Anyone who holds this {3} will surely notice how comfortably it fits in the hand. Given the legends told about {2} and the constant strife they faced, it's no surprise that {0}'s long use of this weapon molded the grip to fit the grasp of a killer.</MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills1_Melee_4>


  <MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills2_Melee_1>Stories told about {2} inevitably touch on two things: their incredible capacity for violence, and the efficiency with which {0} cut through foes using a {3}. Though the name inscribed on the grip has all but faded, there is no question that this {3} is the very weapon which once belonged to {1}.</MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills2_Melee_1>

  <MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills2_Melee_2>In watering holes across the Rim, hushed stories are told of {0} and the countless lives they ended. Though some of the legends have surely grown to be far larger than life, the condition of this {3} clearly shows that {1} was an adept killer of men.</MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills2_Melee_2>

  <MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills2_Melee_3>This {3} feels as if it is radiating an unnatural need for blood. Merely holding it in your hand calls to mind tales of the legendary butcher {0} of {2}, urging the wielder to ever greater feats of slaughter.</MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills2_Melee_3>


  <MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills3_Melee_1>This {3} does strike true
as {1} brings death anew
If they decide
to have your hide
They'll make their clothes of you!</MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills3_Melee_1>

  <MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills3_Melee_2>A palpable sense of menace emanates from this {3}, as if the weapon itself begs to be bathed in the blood of enemies. Simply reading the name {1} inscribed in this weapon sends a chill down the spine, and the stories told of {2} leaves no doubt that this {3} has seen more war than many entire armies.</MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills3_Melee_2>




  <MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills1_Ranged_1>Perhaps {0}, the original wielder of this {3}, liked keeping track of things. Or perhaps they liked to show off. Either way, there are more tally marks etched on this weapon than you can count... hopefully its comfortable grip will enable you to add some more of your own.</MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills1_Ranged_1>

  <MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills1_Ranged_2>Sealed within this {3} lies an ancient and terrible evil! ...Just kidding, it's merely a well-constructed but otherwise normal {3}. Its stock, emblazoned with the name {0}, does fit nicely in your grip, and it is clear that the people of {2} produced weapons ideally suited for killing - rumors of ancient evil notwithstanding.</MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills1_Ranged_2>

  <MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills1_Ranged_3>You've heard many stories about {1}, the headhunter of {2}. It's hard to believe the stories were true, but the sense of bloodlust emenating from this {3} suggests that more than a few people died from this weapon's shots.</MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills1_Ranged_3>

  <MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills1_Ranged_4>Given that this {3} has over a hundred bloodstained notches in its stock, one has to wonder how the people of {2} made so many enemies. Regardless of the reasons, the legends told of {0} and their monstrous ability to gun down said enemies clearly have some truth to them.</MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills1_Ranged_4>


  <MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills2_Ranged_1>  </MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills2_Ranged_1>

  <MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills2_Ranged_2>  </MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills2_Ranged_2>

  <MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills2_Ranged_3>  </MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills2_Ranged_3>


  <MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills3_Ranged_1>  </MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills3_Ranged_1>

  <MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills3_Ranged_2>  </MooMF_MythicStory_HumanKills3_Ranged_2>




  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Shooting_1>The last owner of this {3} claimed that it had been in storage for decades, yet it's still in pristine condition. {0}, the mythical sharpshooter who wielded this weapon, must have taken good care of it. Perhaps that attention to detail is what earned them their reputation as the best shot of {2} and beyond.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Shooting_1>
  
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Shooting_2>The case for this {3} contains not only the weapon itself, but also targets, spare ammunition, repair tools, and cleaning supplies that could cover any conceivable need. It is clear that {0} was not only an excellent shot, but also a master of firearm maintenance and someone who deeply appreciated the art of shooting.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Shooting_2>

  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Shooting_3>Accompanying this {3} was hastily sketched advertisement for "{0}'s Firearms" with the slogan "Come let {1} make your gun shoot good!" While it's unclear if this fledgling business ever got off the ground, there's no question that {0} was an expert marksman, and their {3} does indeed "shoot good" to this day.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Shooting_3>




  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Melee_1>There are old bedtime stories about "{1} the Mighty", the greatest fighter who ever lived. Most people thought they were just that - stories - until this weapon showed up. If the engraving on this ancient {3} is to be believed, {2} were a real group of people, and {1} was a paragon of battle among their number.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Melee_1>
  
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Melee_2>Records unearthed from an ancient fighting ring indicate that one fighter, {0}, went undefeated in nearly a hundred melee fights of various styles. It's unclear whether these feats were accomplished prior to, during, or after {1}'s time in the Rim, but it is abundantly clear from the condition of this {3} that their martial prowess was no myth.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Melee_2>

  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Melee_3>A popular glitterworld holo-film tells the tale of a depressed colonist named {0}, equipped only with a {3}, who defiantly defends the beleaguered Rimworld colony of {2}. As cannibal tribals, gnashing insectoids, and mechanical nightmares alike fall before their fury, {1} realizes their true purpose is to master melee combat in all its forms, and they eventually ascend in glory to serve the Empire as a master-at-arms. This {3} looks awfully like the one from the story, and its killing prowess indicates it's no mere prop...</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Melee_3>




  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Construction_1>No matter how many times you empty out the pockets of this {3}, you always seem to find another nail, screw, or piece of wire. You aren't sure if it's magical, or if the master builder known as {0} just stuffed more random building scraps into this thing than you expected to be possible. Whatever the truth, this {3} has seen the rise of humble abodes and grand monuments alike.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Construction_1>
  
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Construction_2>After being excavated, researchers noted that ruins of the colony of {2} have one peculiarity: nearly every brick, beam, and board seems to be signed or stamped with the name of one "{0}." Anyone wearing this {3}, likewise stamped as once being property of {1}, will surely be inspired by their tenacity and attention to detail in construction.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Construction_2>

  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Construction_3>Although not well-preserved, the ruins of the {2} colony show remarkable craftsmanship, and historians are quick to note that nearly every structure present was made to the precise specifications of their chief engineer {0}. This {3}, also recovered from the ruins, remains in extremely good condition, a fact likely also due to {1}'s exacting nature.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Construction_3>




  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Mining_1>The words "Who needs the sun?" are just barely legible on a faded patch on this {3}. Perhaps that philosophy drove {0} to become the best miner anyone has ever heard of. Supposedly the great halls of {2} were all dug out by {1}'s own hands.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Mining_1>
  
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Mining_2>Legendary colonies such as {2} require countless resources, and when it came to mining them, none were more renowned than {0}. This {3} that once belonged to them is host to numerous patches and repairs, yet still flows around the wearer flawlessly as they swing a pick into compacted steel.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Mining_2>

  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Mining_3>  </MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Mining_3>




  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Cooking_1>Some of your colonists find this {3} unnerving, as despite repeated washes, the smell of tasty food still accompanies anyone wearing it. This might be because this {3} supposedly belonged to the interstellar gourmet sensation known simply as {1}.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Cooking_1>
  
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Cooking_2>To this day, gourmet restaurants across the Rim are rated according to a system of one to three "{1} Stars." While some insist {1} was the founder of a tire company, the truth is that they belonged to a colony known as {2}, where they prepared gourmet meals day in and day out wearing this very {3}.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Cooking_2>

  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Cooking_3>Some tell stories of how much of a menace {0} could be in the kitchen - strutting around in this {3} as they called fellow colonists "idiot sandwiches" or insisting that even the most perfectly cooked meat was "fookin raw." However, none among {2} could deny that the meals {1} produced were of the highest quality, and they remain respected as a chef across the Rim to this day.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Cooking_3>




  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Plants_1>This {3} is covered in uncleanable dirt stains - a testament to the dedication of {1} the Green-Thumbed. It's said the people of {2} never went hungry thanks to {0}'s skill, and if the number of loose seeds still leaking out of the pockets of this {3} are any evidence, there's probably a kernel (heh) of truth to those tales.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Plants_1>
  
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Plants_2>Some people are simply blessed with the ability to make plants flourish, and few across the galaxy were moreso gifted than {0}. Legends tell tales of the bounteous harvests the people of {2} enjoyed due to {1}'s skilled tending. Hopefully some of their skill transfers to you as you wear this {3} bearing their name.

  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Plants_3>Despite being caked in a layer of soil that no scrubbing could ever fully clean off, these {3} fit perfectly and afford the utmost ease when gardening. It's clear that {1}, whose name adorns the {3} like a flower atop a stem, used them to expertly cultivate plants for the entire colony of {2}.





  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Animals_1>DNA analysis has concluded that the fur stuck in this {3} originates from no less than a dozen different animal species. Perhaps the stories of {1} the great animal-whisperer were actually true after all.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Animals_1>
  
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Animals_2>Animal husbandry textbooks have countless techniques named after {0}, and nearly every image in such volumes pictures them wearing these {3}. Perhaps if you don them yourself you will gain a measure of {1}'s fabled ability to pacify and tend to animals of all types.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Animals_2>

  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Animals_3>  </MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Animals_3>




  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Crafting_1>Just holding {0}'s old {3} makes your fingers twitch with the desire to make something, anything. Apparently the instincts of {1}, the greatest crafter from the fabled civilization of {2}, have saturated the very gear they once used.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Crafting_1>
  
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Crafting_2>The name {0} appears in hobbyist handbooks everywhere, from weapon fabrication manuals to garment sewing patterns. This {3}, recovered from the ruins of {2} and itself undoubtably originally crafted by {1}'s deft hands, imbues the wearer with the uncanny desire to take things apart and put them back together again.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Crafting_2>

  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Crafting_3>Nearly everything recovered from the ruins of the {2} colony, including this {3}, bears the name {1}. It seems this one person was responsible for creating or overseeing the creation of nearly everything the colony used, a feat wearing this {3} compels you to match.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Crafting_3>




  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Artistic_1>Some of the most expensive sculptures in interstellar history were made by {0} of {2}. Most people thought this name was an alias, but the faded name painted on this {3} suggests otherwise. Just wearing {1}'s clothing seems to magically produce paint stains and marble dust everywhere, but also instills a creative drive to meet the expectations everyone knows {1} would have of one wearing their attire.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Artistic_1>

  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Artistic_2>Despite living most of their creative life on a nondescript Rim planet, {0} has a clear place in the pantheon of legendary artists of the galaxy. Their name circulates often as one of the all-time greats, and wearing this {3} that once belonged to them is sure to inspire anyone to reach that same lofty pinnacle of artistic talent.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Artistic_2>

  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Artistic_3>{0} of {2} was a sculpture and painting master so widely known, so universally beloved, that they recieved the highest honor an artist can receive: having a children's cartoon turtle named after them. Though these {3} once belonging to {0} will not bestow ninja powers or a radical protective shell, they definitely inspire the wearer to live up to the standards {1}'s enduring works of art represent.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Artistic_3>




  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Medicine_1>This {3} was once worn by {1}, the grand surgeon of {2}. The countless tally marks on the sleeve evoke those use to track kills, but are actually more likely to be a chronicle of lives saved... or perhaps organs harvested.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Medicine_1>
  
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Medicine_2>{0} is well-known in the medical community, as an entire subfield of emergency anesthetic and amputation techniques bears their name. Although this is just an ordinary {3}, seeing the weathered name "{1}" on the breast pocket brings huge measure of confidence to anyone performing those very procedures.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Medicine_2>

  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Medicine_3>Awash in a sea of shot, bruised, and cut colonists, it is said that the community of {2} would have surely fallen in days were it not for the efforts of one heroic doctor named {0}. This {3} bearing their name has been bleached nearly white after being sterilized countless times, but wearing it nonetheless imbues you with {1}'s legendary sense of aesculapian pride.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Medicine_3>




  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Social_1>Everyone knows stories about the Bard of {2}. Supposedly they could pacify mechs with words, peacefully trade with cannibal tribes, and married into the High Stellarch's family. Perhaps {1}, the Bard's real name, exaggerated a few of those stories, but their charismatic energy still clings to this {3}.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Social_1>

  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Social_2>Though the colony of {2} has long been lost to time, tales of {1}'s bright smile and welcoming demeanor still circulate the Rim to this day. Seeing someone wearing this fine {3} inevitably brightens anyone's day, and it is almost as if the clothes themselves compel the wearer to live up to the legends of {1}'s hospitality.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Social_2>
  
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Social_3>Legends say {1} wore the freshest clothes, ate at the chillest restaurants, and hung out with the hottest dudes. They were jacked and anybody who talked shit about them was pathetic. Nobody would say shit to {1}, and now that you're wearing their {3}, the same can be said of you.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Social_3>




  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Intellectual_1>{1} is a name that's rarely heard of nowadays, usually only mentioned among drunk researchers as a supposed intellectual savant who once mastered ancient archotech. This {3} is perhaps the first evidence that they were a real person, and that the long-lost people of {2} really did play host to such an exceptional mind.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Intellectual_1>

  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Intellectual_2>{0} was never a huge name in the research community, credited in only a few papers that rarely circlate the Rim. Among those in the know, however, {1} had a stellar reputation for the unmatched brilliance of their work, and the condition of this {3} indicates they probably spent more time implementing their research at home with the people of {2} rather than authoring scholarly articles.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Intellectual_2>

  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Intellectual_3>The name {0} appears in archotechnology textbooks of all levels, but few traces have ever been found of {2} or the researcher that propelled them into an intellectual renaissance. The badge on this {3} clearly reads "{1}" however, and anyone with the rare honor to wear the clothes {0} once did is sure to be inspired to achieve intellectually as they once did.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Intellectual_3>




  <MooMF_MythicStory_Kills_Thrumbos_1>Stories of {1} turn up in tribal folklore, where {0} is feared as a slayer of nature spirits. Depending on your view of thrumbos, that might be true, as this {3} is decorated with the bones of at least three of the giant beasts.</MooMF_MythicStory_Kills_Thrumbos_1>
  
  <MooMF_MythicStory_ThrumboFriend_1>Many tribes around the Rim worship someone known only as 'wise-friend {1}'. Myths about this character can be traced back to the lost settlements of {2}, whose people supposedly knew how to tame the majestic thrumbos. This thurmbofur-covered {3} seems to uphold those stories.</MooMF_MythicStory_ThrumboFriend_1>



  
  <MooMF_MythicDescription_SpaceVictory_1>It is said that the people of {2} were one of the few groups of Rimworlders to have the resources, brains, and tenacity to build or find a spaceship and successfully leave their planet. Any traces of their civilization are now long gone, and even those from their original planet do not know where they went. This {3} from escapee {1} is evidence that they might have landed and re-settled right here.</MooMF_MythicDescription_SpaceVictory_1>

</LanguageData>