<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>
  <MooMF_LogPrefix>Moo Mythic Items:</MooMF_LogPrefix>
  
  <MooMF_SettingsLabel>Moo's Mythic Framework Settings and Controls</MooMF_SettingsLabel>
  <MooMF_SettingsTitle>Moo's Mythic Framework Settings</MooMF_SettingsTitle>
  <MooMF_ClearAllSavedItemsDescription>Deletes all saved mythic items.</MooMF_ClearAllSavedItemsDescription>
  <MooMF_ClearAllSavedItemsButton>Clear Saved Mythic Items</MooMF_ClearAllSavedItemsButton>
  <MooMF_FlagNotifyItemCreation>Notify player when mythic item is created.</MooMF_FlagNotifyItemCreation>
  <MooMF_PrintExtraStartupDebugLogs>Print Extra Startup Logs</MooMF_PrintExtraStartupDebugLogs>
  <MooMF_FlagAllowMythicItemCreation>Allow Mythic Item Saving.</MooMF_FlagAllowMythicItemCreation>
  <MooMF_FlagAllowMythicItemSpawning>Allow Mythic Item Spawning.</MooMF_FlagAllowMythicItemSpawning>
  <MooMF_MaxMythicItemsProducedPerColony>Max Mythic Items Produced Per Colony:</MooMF_MaxMythicItemsProducedPerColony>
  <MooMF_MaxMythicItemsSaved>Max Saved Mythic Items</MooMF_MaxMythicItemsSaved>
  <MooMF_MinLevelForSkillItems>Minimum level for skill-based mythic items.</MooMF_MinLevelForSkillItems>
  <MooMF_MinLevelForSkillItemsToolTip>Upon leveling up a skill, the mod will try to create a mythic item if the new level is at least this value. Only creates an item once per skill per pawn.</MooMF_MinLevelForSkillItemsToolTip>
  <MooMF_MaxItemOccurence>Mythic Item Occurrence Limit: </MooMF_MaxItemOccurence>
  <MooMF_MaxItemOccurenceTooltip>This value controls how many times a mythic item can show up in any capacity (as a quest reward, as a random shop item, etc) before it is removed from the saved list of mythic items. If set to 0, then mythic items won't be removed unless the total mythic item save limit is reached, in which case the oldest items are removed first.</MooMF_MaxItemOccurenceTooltip>
  <MooMF_PrintDebugLogs>Enable Debug Logging</MooMF_PrintDebugLogs>
  <MooMF_CreateRandomItemsIfNeeded>Create Random Mythic Items If Needed</MooMF_CreateRandomItemsIfNeeded>
  <MooMF_CreateRandomItemsIfNeededToolTip>If this is enabled, and the game tries to make a mythic items but finds no valid saved options, create a random mythic item based on some hard-coded preset options.</MooMF_CreateRandomItemsIfNeededToolTip>
  
  <MooMF_ManualSaveButton>save button pressed</MooMF_ManualSaveButton>
  <MooMF_ManualLoadBUtton>load button pressed</MooMF_ManualLoadBUtton>

  <MooMF_FailedToCreateLIFromDebug>Tried to place a saved mythic item via debug actions, but failed to create one. There's probably no saved mythic items right now.</MooMF_FailedToCreateLIFromDebug>

  <MooMF_CreatedNewItemMessage>{0} achievements have caused their {1} to become a mythic item! The recorded reason for their mythic was '{2}'</MooMF_CreatedNewItemMessage>

  <MooMF_AddMythicRelic>Add Mythic Relic</MooMF_AddMythicRelic>
  <MooMF_NoSavedMythicOptionsForRelics>No Saved Mythic Items Available</MooMF_NoSavedMythicOptionsForRelics>
  
  <MooMF_MythicPrefix>\n\nMythic: </MooMF_MythicPrefix>
  <!--In mythic stories, the following variables always apply to the following features
    0 = the original owner's full name
    1 = the original owners nickname, or first name if they don't have one
    2 = the original owner's faction
    3 = normal item label 
    For titles, only 2 inputs are given:
    0 = original owners nickname
    1 = normal item label
    -->
  <MooMF_MythicStory_100Kills_Melee_1>It's said that {0} of {2}, the original owner of this {3}, killed over 100 people. That seems farfetched, but it's undeniable that this weapon has seen untold battles. No one can fully clean off all the blood stains, and there's a palpable sense of menace emenating from the weapon. This {3} has seen more war than most people ever will.</MooMF_MythicStory_100Kills_Melee_1>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_100Kills_Melee_2>No one believed the stories about them, but this {3} is stark evidence of what the people of {2} were capable of. The name {1} is carved into the handle of this {3}, just barely legible beneath untold years of dirt and grime. </MooMF_MythicStory_100Kills_Melee_2>

  
  <MooMF_MythicStory_100Kills_Ranged_1>Perhaps {0}, the original wielder of this {3}, liked keeping track of things. Or perhaps they liked to show off. Either way, this weapon is etched with more tally marks than you can count. Hopefully you'll be able to add some more of your own.</MooMF_MythicStory_100Kills_Ranged_1>
  <MooMF_MythicStory_100Kills_Ranged_2>You've heard many stories about {1}, the headhunter of {2}. It's hard to believe the stories were true, but the bloodlust emenating from this {3} suggests that more than a few people died from this weapon's shots.</MooMF_MythicStory_100Kills_Ranged_2>

  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Shooting>The last owner of this {3} claimed that it had been in storage for decades, yet it's still in pristine condition. {0}, the mythical sharpshooter who wielded this weapon, must have taken good care of it. Perhaps that attention to detail is what earned them their reputation as the best shot of {2} and beyond.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Shooting>

  
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Melee>There are old bedtime stories about "{1} the mighty", the greatest fighter who ever lived. Most people thought they were just that - stories - until this weapon showed up. If the engraving on this ancient {3} is to be believed, {2} were a real group of people, and {1} was a paragon of battle among their number.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Melee>

  
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Construction>No matter how many times you empty out the pockets of this {3}, you always seem to find another nail, screw, or piece of wire. You aren't sure if it's magical, or if the master builder known as {0} just stuffed more random building scraps into this thing than you expected to be possible. Whatever the truth, this {3} has seen the rise of grand monuments.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Construction>

  
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Mining>The words "Who needs the sun?" are just barely legible on a faded patch on this {3}. Perhaps that philosophy drove {0} to become the best miner anyone has ever heard of. Supposedly the great halls of {2} were all dug out by {1}'s own hands.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Mining>

  
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Cooking>Some of your colonists find this {3} unnerving. Despite repeated washes, the smell of a tasty feast still clings to this clothing. This {3} supposedly belonged to the interstellar gourmet sensation known simply as {0}.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Cooking>

  
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Plants>This {3} is covered in uncleanable dirt stains - a testament to the dedication of {1} the green-thumbed. It's said the people of {2} never went hungry thanks to {0}'s skill, and if the number of loose seeds still leaking out of the pockets of this {3} are any evidence, there's probably a kernel (heh) or truth to those tales.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Plants>

  
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Animals>DNA analysis has concluded that the fur stuck in this {3} originated from no less than a dozen different animal species. Perhaps the stories of {1} the great animal-whisperer were actually true after all.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Animals>
 
  
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Crafting>Just holding {0}'s old {3} makes your fingers twitch with the desire to make something, anything. Apparently the instincts of {1}, the greatest crafter from the fabled civilization of {2}, were passed into his gear.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Crafting>

  
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Artistic>Some of the most expensive sculptures in interstellar history were made by {2}'s {1}. Most people thought this name was an alias, but the faded name painted on this {3} suggests otherwise. Just wearing {0}'s clothing seems to magically produce paint stains and marble dust everywhere, but it also instills a creative drive to meet the expectations you know {0} would have  </MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Artistic>

  
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Medicine>This {3} was once worn by {1}, the grand surgeon of {2}. The countless tally marks on the {3}, originally thought to be kill-marks, are actually more likely to be lives saved (or maybe organs harvested).</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Medicine>

  
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Social>Everyone knows stories about the Bard of {2}. Supposedly they could pacify mechs with words, peacefully trade with cannibal tribes, and married into the High Stellarch's family. Perhaps {1}, the Bard's real name, exaggerated a few of those stories, but their charismatic energy still lingers to this {3}.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Social>

  
  <MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Intellectual>{1} is a named that's rarely heard of nowadays. They're mentioned by cryptic archotechs when modern researchers try to uncover their original creators. Apparently their brilliance was unmmatched, and this {3} is perhaps the first evidence that they were a real person from the long-lost advanced people of {2}, and not just a story told among archotechs.</MooMF_MythicStory_Mastery_Intellectual>


  <MooMF_MythicStory_Kills_Thrumbos_1>Stories of {1} turn up in tribal folklore, where {0} is feared as a slayer of nature spirits. Depending on your view of thrumbos, that might be true, as his {3} is decorated with the bones of at least three differnt thrumbos.</MooMF_MythicStory_Kills_Thrumbos_1>


  <MooMF_MythicStory_ThrumboFriend_1>Many tribes around the Rim worship someone known only as 'wise-friend {1}'. Myths about this character can be traced back to the lost settlements of {2}, whose people supposedly knew how to tame the majestic thrumbos. This thurmbofur-covered {3} seems to uphold those stories.</MooMF_MythicStory_ThrumboFriend_1>

  <!--Effect description notes: 
   - these are added to the in-game description of mythic items, after the flavor string.
   - The element {0} should always be the label of the mythic item itself (ex: Revolver).
   - All other elements can vary depending on what subtype of mythic effect def uses these,
   although {1} should try to be the label of whatever is added to this weapon, if applicable. -->
  <MooMF_AbilityDescription_Addon>\n\nMythic Effect: {0}</MooMF_AbilityDescription_Addon>
  <MooMF_AbilityDescription_GrantStatAbility>Grants the user a buff called "{1}", which increases their performance in the relevant ability.,</MooMF_AbilityDescription_GrantStatAbility>
  <MooMF_AbilityDescription_GrantThurmboButcher>Grants the user the "{1}" buff, which doubles their butcher yield's from thrumbos.</MooMF_AbilityDescription_GrantThurmboButcher>
  <MooMF_AbilityDescription_MechDrops>This weapon makes the user unusually good at dismantling mechanoids. Mechanoid kills will drop extra steel, among other things.</MooMF_AbilityDescription_MechDrops>
  <MooMF_AbilityDescription_InsectDrops>This weapon grants the user a supernatural ability to find extra insect jelly when hunting insects, which is dropped whenever they kill an insect. Just don't ask where it comes from.</MooMF_AbilityDescription_InsectDrops>
  <MooMF_AbilityDescription_Thrumbocall>This item grants the user the "{1}" ability to summon a thrumbo herd once a year. This effect has no impact on normal Thrumbo migration frequencies.</MooMF_AbilityDescription_Thrumbocall>
  <MooMF_AbilityDescription_APRocket>This weapon has a small shrapnel rocket jury-rigged onto it, granting the "{1}" ability. This can be used once a day deal heavy damage to unarmored foes.</MooMF_AbilityDescription_APRocket>
  <MooMF_AbilityDescription_EMPRocket>This weapon has a small EMP cannon jury-rigged onto it, granting the "{1}" ability. This can be used once a day quadrum tom immobolize a large cluster of mechanoids for significantly more time than other EMP weapons.</MooMF_AbilityDescription_EMPRocket>
  <MooMF_AbilityDescription_KillstreakDR>While equipped, this weapon's user enters a battle trance every time they kill something, granting damage resistance. Subsequent kills before it wears off will increase the effect.</MooMF_AbilityDescription_KillstreakDR>
  <MooMF_AbilityDescription_KillstreakFirerate>While equipped, this weapon's user enters a battle trance every time they kill something, granting improved fire rates and firing cooldown. Subsequent kills before it wears off will increase the effect.</MooMF_AbilityDescription_KillstreakFirerate>

>
  <MooMF_MythicDescription_SpaceVictory1>It is said that the people of {2} were one of the few groups of people to have the grit, brains, and the metaphysical patience to build or find a spaceship and successfully get off a Rimworld. No one from their original planet knows where they went. This {3} from escapee {1} is evidence that they eventually reached another planet. Maybe it was this one in the distant past.</MooMF_MythicDescription_SpaceVictory1>







</LanguageData>