<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Mooloh's Mythic Framework</name>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.3</li>
	</supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
      <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
    <li>
      <packageId>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.Core</packageId>
      <displayName>Vanilla Expanded Framework</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1854607105</steamWorkshopUrl>
    </li>
	</modDependencies> 

	<loadAfter>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Royalty</li>
    <li>brrainz.harmony</li>
    <li>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.Core</li>
	</loadAfter>
	<author>Mooloh</author>

	<packageId>mooloh.mythicitems</packageId>

  <description>Chronicles the triumphs of your colonists by creating 'Mythic Items' based on their achievements. Mythic Items are weapons and apparel with special names, descriptions, and abilities. They appear in your OTHER colonies as quest rewards.

&lt;size=24&gt;Overview&lt;/size&gt;

I play a lot of Dungeons and Dragons, so I believe that what makes an item 'legendary' is NOT just the quality of the item when it is first assembled. What really matters are the stories and events that an item has been involved in. In other words, something should be legendary because it has legends about it! However, since the words 'legendary', 'relic', and 'artifact' are already used in this game, I'm calling these storied items 'mythic items'.
 
To that end, this mod waits for your colonists to achieve impressive feats. When that happens, it creates a mythic item based on that colonist's weapon or clothing. This mythic item is a legendary version of the original item, with a unique name, description, and ability that pertain to whatever the colonist did to earn their reputation. Once mythic items have been created, this mod will occasionally spawn those mythic items as quest rewards once you start a new colony, There they will serve as a reminder your prior achievements while also giving your new colony a unique boost.

&lt;size=24&gt;Installing&lt;/size&gt;

This mod is safe to add and remove from existing saves. If it's removed from an existing game, any mythic items in the game will revert to normal items. Saved mythic items (that could potentially be generated in new games) are not removed upon disabling the mod, but can be manually cleared in the settings.

If a saved mythic item becomes invalid (EX: because you disabled the mod that a mythic item's actual item is from), that mythic item will be stored in a backup file. You can manually try to reload such items in this mod's settings.

&lt;size=24&gt;Mythic Creation&lt;/size&gt;

Mythic Items can be created and saved whenever a colonist meets one of the following conditions, assuming the colonist in question does not already have a mythic item equipped:

 - A colonist kills enough humanoids, mechanoids, insects, or thrumbos. Kill thresholds differ between categories and can be scaled up or down in the settings. Some categories have multiple thresholds which replace/upgrade the resulting mythic item. I tried to balance the thresholds such that you'll usually hit the first threshold on your best combat colonist within three years on medium/hard difficulty.

 - A colonist reaches level 20 in a skill.

 - A colonist tames their second thrumbo.

 - A colonist escapes the Rim (AKA they are part of any vanilla or DLC ending. Only one colonist is selected per victory to make a mythic item).

 - Want to commemorate your own events? Research the 'Myth Making' technology and sculpt a myth maker item. This very expensive item lets you manually produce mythic items if you feel that your colonists' achievements merit one.

&lt;size=24&gt;Finding Mythic Items&lt;/size&gt;

Once you've played the game enough and have produced a few mythic items, these items can show up in subsequent games in several ways. Bear in mind that mythic items can only show up ONCE per world, and after showing up in a few worlds, a given mythic item will disappear entirely. 

 - The simplest way to find mythic items is through normal quest reward. Mythic items will only generate as quest rewards after at least a year has passed in the current colony, and it is as common as the vanilla reward for masterwork/legendary items.

 - If you are allied with a faction, you can pay 7500 silver and a ton of goodwill to create a quest to find a mythic item (this works like the AI persona core quest). This option is only available after the current colony has survived at least 90 days.

 - If Ideology is installed, a mythic item can be selected as an Ideoligion relic. This does not remove the selected mythic item from the list of currently saved mythic items, that way you can use a mythic item in multiple Ideologions. This can lead to duplicate mythic items in the same world - one as a relic and one as a normal quest reward. That seemed worth it to allow for relic/mythic items without rewriting too much code.

Note: Multiple aspects of this can be changed in the mod;s settings, like the disappearance rate, and the no-same-world restriction.

&lt;size=24&gt;Mythic Item Effects&lt;/size&gt;

Mythic items can have a variety of effects, and are always of legendary quality. The exact effect depends on the situation that created the mythic item in the first place. Some examples include:

 - A charge rifle with a rocket launcher mounted on the side, which can be fired once every few days.

 - A shirt that grants the wearer the ability to cook Epicurean Delights, a wildly opulent meal that grants a huge buff to people who eat it.

 - A cowboy hat which passively boosts the wearer's mining abilities.

 - A pair of pants which can periodically grant the wearer a creative inspiration.

&lt;size=24&gt;Mod Compatibility&lt;/size&gt;

I don't expect this mod to have too many compatibility issues. The only exceptions are mods which add extra data to weapons and apparel, and mods which mess around with combat. Here's list of mod interactions that I know of. Note: In the case of extra data that's preserved on items (like infusions), you can prevent these values from being used in the mod settings if you're worried about balance.

Compatible: 

 - A Rimworld Of Magic: Custom Enchantments (using Gems) are preserved on mythic items.

 - Infusion (1 and 2): Infusions are preserved on mythic items from both mods. 

 - Infinite Reinforce: Reinforcement values at the time of mythic-ness are preserved.

 - Modded Thrumbos: The following thrumbos count for the purposes of counting kills/tamings: Anima Thrmbos, Archothrumbos, and Royal Thrumbos.

 - Alpha Animals: Black Hive faction insects are counted towards insect kills.

 - Vanilla Expanded Insectoids: Insectoid faction insects are counted towards insect kills.

Unsupported/Unknown:

 - Character Editor: Mythic Items worn by saved pawns stop being mythic, and revert to normal legendary items.

 - Ducks Insane skills: Skill thresholds remain at 20.

 - Combat Extended: I don't play with this mod, so I'm not sure how the combat abilities this mod adds will interact with CE. If someone tries it out and lets me know that there are issues, I'll look into it.

&lt;size=24&gt;Other considerations&lt;/size&gt;

I'm not a good creative writer, nor am I a good editor. Despite that, I somehow convinced myself to write and proofread a LOT of flavor text. There's probably some grammar errors that slipped through. If you see one, please feel free to comment about it, and I'll thank you.

I intentionally didn't overwrite the vanilla artwork on legendary items for two reasons: I think the vanilla artwork text is funny and didn't want to remove it, and it would've been tedious to do anyway.

&lt;size=24&gt;Want to make your own types of Mythic Items?&lt;/size&gt;

I designed this mod with other modders in mind. It's possible to add new mythic item titles and descriptions with just XML. It's sometimes possible to add new mythic creation triggers and mythic item effects using just XML, depending on the exact trigger or ability, and minimal coding otherwise.

For more information and a few examples of how you can add your own mythic stuff to a mod, please see the README on the mod's Github: https://github.com/mlholland/MooMythicItems

&lt;size=24&gt;Want to contribute without modding?&lt;/size&gt;

I think this mod would benefit from more than just two people writing flavor text. If you have an idea but don't want to write an entire mod, feel free to post your ideas for titles, descriptions, effects, or triggers in the relevant discussion page ofnthis mod's steam page. If I use them, I'll show my graditude by... thanking you and adding you to the to the contributors list.
   
&lt;size=24&gt;Credits and Thanks&lt;/size&gt;

 - Code: Mooloh

 - Cover art: Erok

 - Thanks for Hi19hi19, who helped brainstorm ideas for mythic effects and abilities, and wrote a bunch of flavor text.

 - Thanks to the RimWorld Discord's modding channel, who helped me figure out how to properly code this.

&lt;size=24&gt;Legal&lt;/size&gt;

  - MIT License: https://github.com/mlholland/MooMythicItems/blob/main/LICENSE

  - Source Code on Github: https://github.com/mlholland/MooMythicItems

&lt;size=24&gt;Changelog&lt;/size&gt;

  - 6/11/2022: v1.0 Initial Release

</description>
</ModMetaData>